## ADAMS ZELAYA

www.linkedin.com/in/adamszelaya, 571-699-8605, Adams.zelaya123@gmail.com, Alexandria, Virginia, 22304

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

- CompTIA Security+ CE
- CompTIA A+ CE
- Google Cybersecurity Professional
- Google IT Support Professional
- CompTIA Network+ (In Progress)

## **SKILLS**

- Cybersecurity
- HTML
- Python
- Linux
- Network Configuration and Management
- Risk Identification and Management
- Data Management and Analysis
- ServiceNow
- Troubleshooting
- Microsoft 365
- Windows
- IT Support
- Driver Installation
- Time Management
- Customer Service/Support
- SQL

## **EDUCATION**

**Bachelors:** Cybersecurity and Information Assurance Western Governors University December 2024

#### **SUMMARY**

Certified, fast-learning, hard-working cybersecurity professional with many years of experience working with tech and knowledge of cybersecurity. Implemented risk management strategies across a hospital setting which included risk mitigation, avoidance and implementing security controls in order to ensure client data integrity. Seeking an entry-level position to utilize my knowledge of threats, security protocols, and risk mitigation as well as develop new skillsets along the way.

## **EXPERIENCE**

## Technical Support Representative (Tier 3), Apr 2023 - Current NIS Inc, DC (Full-Time)

- Proficiency of ServiceNow, Excel, HP DCC, Microsoft 365, Microsoft Teams, and command lines were needed to efficiently complete work tasks.
- Configured TCP/IP, subnet masks, default gateways, and DNS servers onto devices.
- Monitored logs and used different monitoring software in order to determine anomalies found in printer errors.
- Orchestrated the installation, repair, and maintenance of 500+ printers across a hospital network.
- Reduced printer downtime by 30% by implementing preventative maintenance schedules and streamlining repair workflows.
- Successfully sustained a 100% completion rate of tickets contributing to the company's overall success in maintaining a high completion rate.

## Self-Taught, January 2023 - Current

- Self-studied/researched various concepts about networking and security in order to acquire various certifications including CompTIA A+ and Security+.
- Took many unaccredited courses in order to improve knowledge of security concepts.
- Enjoys studying and is always actively learning new information and concepts.

# Mover (IT Technician & Customer Service), Dec 2017 - Mar 2023 IMS, Alexandria, VA (Full-Time)

- Provided technical support for computers, TVs, and printers w in order to properly transport them.
- Demonstrated professionalism for high-profile clients and properly managed PII.
- Contributed to company success by leading teams while working with different embassies which lead to renewed contracts.
- Increased team efficiency by 20% by supervising team and creating a positive work environment.